<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20140725</CreaDate><CreaTime>00000000</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20140725</ModDate><ModTime>00000000</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>100000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><dataIdInfo><idPurp>HydroBASINS data provides a series of polygon layers that depict watershed boundaries and sub-basin delineations at a global scale. The goal of this product is to provide a seamless global coverage of consistently sized and hierarchically nested sub-basins at different scales (from tens to millions of square kilometers), supported by a coding scheme that allows for analysis of watershed topology such as up- and downstream connectivity.</idPurp><idCitation><resTitle>HydroBASINS Asia, Level 3, Version 1.c - Sub-basins in standard format (without lakes)</resTitle></idCitation><searchKeys><keyword>HydroBASINS</keyword><keyword>HydrSHEDS</keyword></searchKeys><dataExt><geoEle xmlns=""><GeoBndBox esriExtentType="search"><westBL>57</westBL><eastBL>151</eastBL><northBL>56</northBL><southBL>1</southBL><exTypeCode>1</exTypeCode></GeoBndBox></geoEle></dataExt><resConst><Consts><useLimit>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;HydroBASINS is covered by the same License Agreement as the HydroSHEDS database, which is available at &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.hydrosheds.org"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;http://www.hydrosheds.org&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;. For all regulations regarding license grants, copyright, redistribution restrictions, required attributions, disclaimer of warranty, indemnification, liability, waiver of damages, and a precise definition of licensed materials, please refer to the License Agreement. By downloading and using the data the user agrees to the terms and conditions of the License Agreement.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</useLimit></Consts></resConst><idCredit>The HydroBASINS product has been developed on behalf of World Wildlife Fund US (WWF), with support and in collaboration with the EU BioFresh project, Berlin, Germany; the International Union for Conservation of Nature (IUCN), Cambridge, UK; and McGill University, Montreal, Canada. We kindly ask users to cite HydroBASINS in any published material produced using the data. If possible, online links to the HydroSHEDS website (http://www.hydrosheds.org) should be provided. Citations and acknowledgements of the HydroBASINS data should be made as follows: Lehner, B., Grill G. (2013): Global river hydrography and network routing: baseline data and new approaches to study the world’s large river systems. Hydrological Processes, 27(15): 2171–2186. Data is available at www.hydrosheds.org.
</idCredit><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;All HydroBASINS layers were derived from World Wildlife Fund’s HydroSHEDS data based on a grid resolution of 15 arc-seconds (approximately 500 m at the equator). Watersheds were delineated in a consistent manner at different scales, and a hierarchical sub-basin breakdown was created following the topological concept of the Pfafstetter coding system. The resulting polygon layers are termed HydroBASINS and represent a subset of the HydroSHEDS database. This shapefile contains (sub-)basin polygons for Asia at Pfafstetter level 3.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs></dataIdInfo></metadata>
